https://www.advantageballoons.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content HomeEvent TypesServicesRooftop BalloonsContact
HomeEvent TypesServicesRooftop BalloonsContact Privacy Policy
Who we areWe are PCA Promotions, INC dba Advantage Balloons & Promotions. We operate out of 2237 W. Division St. Arlington, TX 76012. You can contact us at 817-261-1989 or by email at info@advantageballoons.comWhat personal data we collect and why we collect itContact formsWe use the information you provide to us in the contact form to create your order and to stay in contact with you regarding your order. We currently do not send mass emails or use your contact information for marketing purposes. We use Contact Form 7 for the form.CookiesIf you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.Embedded content from other websites or Third Party AppsPages on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWe use Google Analytics and Google Ads to monitor site usage and statistics and do not use any information for any other purpose.How long we retain your dataFor users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Additional informationHow we protect your dataWe are committed to privacy and collect as little data as possible to do our job and to complete your order.What data breach procedures we have in placeWe do not store any personal information on this website.info@advantageballoons.com817-261-1989Terms & ConditionsPrivacy Policy
Once clicked you will be taken to an Authorize.net checkout page. Follow the directions there to complete the payment.Advantage Balloons & Promotions© 2020 Advantage Balloons & Promotions.
